<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frontpage on opaal model checker</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Frontpage on opaal model checker</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:23:51 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Architecture</title><link>/architecture/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:23:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>/architecture/</guid><description>opaal opaal is a distributed/parallel (discrete time) model checker for networks of timed automata implemented in Python using MPI. opaal is designed to be easily extendible, such that different approaches can be prototyped quickly.
Architecture [image missing]
Presentations Mtlab Workshop9 2010-08-24 (pdf) - An early presentation on the architecture</description></item><item><title>Downloads</title><link>/download/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:23:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>/download/</guid><description> Downloads Please see the install instructions on Installing opaal + LTSmin
Presentations Mtlab Workshop9 2010-08-24 (pdf) An early presentation on the architecture</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:23:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>The people behind opaal was started by Mads Chr. Olesen and Kenneth Yrke Jørgensen a late night at the Department of Computer Science at Aalborg University, after extensive and long discussions about how difficult it would be to implement a parallel/distributed model checker that was easy to experiment with.
Current developers Please contact Mads Chr. Olesen or [Andreas Dalsgaard]()).</description></item><item><title>opaal &#43; LTSmin</title><link>/opaal-ltsmin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:23:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>/opaal-ltsmin/</guid><description>Setup Instructions
This guide is for installing opaal+LTSmin and have been tested on Ubuntu 12.04 and Ubuntu 14.04 but have also been confirmed to work on Arch Linux and Mac OS X - however you will have to identify the needed software packages yourself on those platforms. The installation of opaal+LTSmin is automated so users simply need to download and run a bash script. Besides installation on a PC, this method also support installing of opaal+LTSmin on multiuser system which, e.</description></item></channel></rss>